const novels_team1 = [
  {
    // Book cipher
    question: "Code to unlock the next clue:",
    answer: "chope",
  },
  {
    // Singapore
    question: "Maybe there was something from Singapore? Find the code from the following hints:\n\n" +
      "- Wah, so high ah, can see all the lights one. Famous place, got big boat on top also.\n" +
      "- Must sit down, drink kopi O and makan your toast one, confirm old school style.\n" +
      "- Wah, this place shiok to go jalan jalan and shopping. All the branded stuff here.",
    answer: "q2a",
  },
  {
    question: "Getting bored? Click <a target='_blank' href='https://mywordle.strivemath.com/?word=oijkt'>here<a> to play a game!",
    answer: "sushi",
    message: "Where'd the sushi go? I think Heather was craving some wasabi..."
  }
]

const novels_team2 = [
  {
    // Book cipher
    question: "Code to unlock the next clue:",
    answer: "shiok",
  },
  {
    // Singapore
    question: "Maybe there was something from Singapore? Find the code from the following hints:\n\n" +
      "- Hungry ah? Go this hawker centre can eat all the seafoodâ€”famous for chilli crab one!\n" +
      "- Where to see lions and tigers when the sun go down ah? This one, very exciting.\n" +
      "- Here got the tallest hill in Singapore. Hike until sweaty but confirm can see monkeys.",
    answer: "62j",
  },
  {
    question: "Getting bored? Click <a target='_blank' href='https://mywordle.strivemath.com/?word=oijkt'>here<a> to play a game!",
    answer: "sushi",
    message: "Where'd the sushi go? I think Heather was craving some tempura..."
  }
]
const novels_team3 = [
  {
    // Book cipher
    question: "Code to unlock the next clue:",
    answer: "kiasu",
  },
  {
    // Singapore
    question: "Maybe there was something from Singapore? Find the code from the following hints:\n\n" +
      "- This place ah, look like durian one. Got all the artsy shows inside.\n" +
      "- Wah, night market here! Got everything to makan, and sell clothes, toys all that.\n" +
      "- Aiyoh, need buy instant noodles or snacks? The little shop downstairs sure got.",
    answer: "j710",
  },
  {
    question: "Getting bored? Click <a target='_blank' href='https://mywordle.strivemath.com/?word=oijkt'>here<a> to play a game!",
    answer: "sushi",
    message: "Where'd the sushi go? I think Heather was craving some sashimi..."
  }
]
